O.W. Riegel Papers WLU.Coll.0387
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
- Personal Publicity, 1937-1977; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); .417 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 1-37)
  - Personal Publicity, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Personal Publicity, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Post-War Travel, 1946-1989; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); 2.83 Linear Feet 4 Boxes: 2 storage boxes, 1 standard archival box, and 1 small archival box (Box 1-4, Folder 1-93)
  Materials in this series consist of items Riegel acquired while traveling after World War II. Riegel went to several european nations during the Cold War including Yugoslavia, Bulgaria, Romania, Czechoslovakia, Poland, Hungary, Italy, East Germany, Germany, and Britain. Throughout his journeys, Riegel retained numerous maps, brochures, publications, and pamphlets of places and events he attended.
  - Correspondence, 1963-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1-16)
    This subseries concerns Riegel's correspondence during his travels in Eastern Europe and focuses primarily on upcoming european film festivals and catching up with friend and acquaintences while abroad.
    - Correspondence: Bal-Cas, 1963-1984 (Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Cat-Drw, 1963-1984 (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Ede-Flo, 1963-1984 (Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: For-Hit, 1963-1984 (Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Hus-Jan, 1963-1984 (Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Joh-Lau, 1963-1984 (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Loj-Oso, 1963-1984 (Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Pas-San, 1963-1984 (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Sch-Squ, 1963-1984 (Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Swi-Ter, 1963-1984 (Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Urb-Zan, 1963-1984 (Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Misc., 1963-1965 (Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Misc., 1966-1970 (Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Misc., 1979-1981 (Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Misc., 1981-1989 (Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Misc., 1963-1984 (Folder 16)
  - Domestic, 1946-1984 (Box 1, Folder 17-33)
    Items in this subseries focus on the US in relation to Riegel's travel after World War II. some items of note include maps of San Francisco, CA and Madison, WI, assorted brochures from various city centers, and a couple of sketches.
    - Financial Documents, 1981-1984 (Folder 17)
    - Maps, 1965-1984 (Folder 18)
    - Maps: Amended, 1965-1984 (Folder 19)
    - Maps: Misc., 1965-1984 (Folder 20)
    - Personal Affects, 1965-1984 (Folder 21)
    - Publications, 1974-1978 (Folder 22)
    - Publications, 1980-1981 (Folder 23)
    - Publications, 1981-1983 (Folder 24)
    - Publications, 1984 (Folder 25)
    - Publications June, 1984 (Folder 26)
    - Publications June-Aug., 1984 (Folder 27)
    - Publications Misc., 1965-1984 (Folder 28)
    - Publications Misc., 1965-1984 (Folder 29)
    - Publications Misc., 1965-1984 (Folder 30)
    - Publications Misc., 1965-1984 (Folder 31)
    - Publications Misc., 1965-1984 (Folder 32)
    - Publications Misc., 1965-1984 (Folder 33)
  - International, 1946-1989 (Box 1-3, Folder 34-87)
    This subseries consists of iteme Riegel acquired during his international travel. Most items are from Eastern Europe, but there are a couple of items from Western Europe and a publication from Australia.
    - Brochures and Pamphlets, 1946-1989 (Box 1-2, Folder 34-44)
      Items in this subseries consist of pamphlets and brochures related to Riegel's travels throughout Europe. some publications of note include lodging brochures from Bulgaria and Romania and hungarian recreational brochures.
      - Australia-Bulgaria, 1946-1989 (Folder 34)
      - Britain, 1946-1989 (Folder 35)
      - Britain-France, 1946-1989 (Folder 36)
      - Germany, 1946-1989 (Folder 37)
      - Germany, 1946-1989 (Folder 38)
      - Holland-Hungary, 1946-1989 (Folder 39)
      - Hungary, 1946-1989 (Folder 40)
      - Italy, 1946-1989 (Folder 41)
      - Poland, Romania, Spain, Switzerland, Virgin Islands, 1946-1989 (Folder 42)
      - Yugoslavia, 1946-1989 (Folder 43)
      - Yugoslavia, 1946-1989 (Folder 44)
    - Financial Documents, 1966-1989 (Box 2, Folder 45-53)
      Items in this subseries consist of the receipts and charges Riegel kept from his travels in europe.
      - Financial Documents, 1966 (Folder 45)
      - Financial Documents, 1966-1968 (Folder 46)
      - Financial Documents Jul.-Sep., 1968 (Folder 47)
      - Financial Documents, 1968-1970 (Folder 48)
      - Financial Documents, 1974-1980 (Folder 49)
      - Financial Documents, 1980-1989 (Folder 50)
      - Financial Documents Misc., 1966-1989 (Folder 51)
      - Financial Documents Misc., 1966-1989 (Folder 52)
      - Financial Documents Misc., 1966-1989 (Folder 53)
    - Government Documents, 1960-1966 (Folder 54)
    - Government Documents, 1968-1970 (Folder 55)
    - Government Documents Misc., 1946-1989 (Folder 56)
    - Maps, 1946-1989 (Box 2, Folder 57-69)
      This subseries consists of maps of various european countries that Riegel traveled through.
      - Maps Amended, 1962-1963 (Folder 57)
      - Maps Amended, 1964-1966 (Folder 58)
      - Maps Amended Misc., 1962-1980 (Folder 59)
      - Bulgaria, 1962-1980 (Folder 60)
      - Bulgaria, 1963-1964 (Folder 61)
      - Czechoslovakia-Denmark, 1962-1980 (Folder 62)
      - England-France, 1962-1980 (Folder 63)
      - Germany, 1962-1980 (Folder 64)
      - Germany, 1962-1980 (Folder 65)
      - Hungary, 1962-1980 (Folder 66)
      - Italy, 1962-1980 (Folder 67)
      - Italy, 1962-1980 (Folder 68)
      - Poland, Romania, Switzerland, Yugoslavia, and Misc., 1962-1980 (Folder 69)
    - Personal Affects, 1946-1989 (Box 2, Folder 70-75)
      Items in this subseries were the personal affects of Oscar Riegel in relation to his post-war European travel. Some items of note include his travel diary and a diary by "Dee", and press membership identification.
      - Boarding Passes/ Diaries, 1946-1989 (Folder 70)
      - Diaries, 1968 (Box 1-2, Folder 70a)
      - Membership & Press, 1946-1989 (Folder 71)
      - Misc., 1946-1989 (Folder 72)
      - Misc., 1946-1989 (Folder 73)
      - Misc., 1946-1989 (Folder 74)
      - Misc., 1946-1989 (Folder 75)
    - Publications, 1946-1989 (Box 3, Folder 76-83)
      This subseries consists of materials printed for the public that Riegel kept from his travels abroad. Some items of note include US embassy guides to Bucharest, Romania and Sofia, Bulgaria, and some magazines from Romania and Poland.
      - Publications, 1943 (Folder 76)
      - Publications, 1963 (Folder 77)
      - Publications, 1963-1964 (Folder 78)
      - Publications, 1966-1968 (Folder 79)
      - Publications, 1968-1969 (Folder 80)
      - Publications, 1969-1970 (Folder 81)
      - Publications Misc., 1963-1989 (Folder 82)
      - Publications Misc., 1963-1989 (Folder 83)
    - Misc., 1946-1989 (Box 3, Folder 84-87)
      - Misc., 1964-1982 (Folder 84)
      - Misc., 1964-1982 (Folder 85)
      - Misc., 1964-1982 (Folder 86)
      - Misc., 1964-1982 (Folder 87)
  - Notes, 1946-1989 (Box 4, Folder 88-93)
    Items in this subseries consist of notes that Riegel prior to and during his trip to Eastern Europe. One item of note is a German quiz he took prior to his departure.
    - Notes, 1951 (Folder 88)
    - Notes, 1957-1976 (Folder 89)
    - Notes, 1978-1983 (Folder 90)
    - Notes Misc., 1946-1989 (Folder 91)
    - Notes Misc., 1946-1989 (Folder 92)
    - Notes Misc., 1946-1989 (Folder 93)
  - Unprocessed Materials, 1946-1976 (Box 4a)
- Projects, 1950-1952; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); 1.99 Linear Feet (Box 1-3, Folder 1-126)
  The items in this series relate to two major projects Riegel conducted in Europe between 1950 and 1952. The first one focused on public opinion in West Germany on a variety of topics, but emphasised government and politics in particular. This project was conducted with assitance in the form of a grant, stipend, and paid travel by the State Departnment. The second project, through Princeton University, focused on the impact of the cross cultural exchange program between Belgium and the United States, with the goal of understanding the opinion Belgians had of the United States after going through the program and then returning to their home country. Contents in this series include: Survey materials from both projects, information on participants in the Belgium study, publications Riegel kept from his time in Europe, his notes on the projects, and financial papers relevant to the projects.
  - W. Germany, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1-22)
    Items in this subseries focus on the West German Cultural Exchange program and its impact on its participants. Items of note include samples of questionaires and surveys and maps of parts of West Germany.
    - Correspondence: All-Cre, 1950-1952 (Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Dix-Esp, 1950-1952 (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Family, 1950 (Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Family Jul.-Aug., 1950 (Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Family Sep., 1950 (Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Gal-Ley, 1950-1952 (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: McA-Ric, 1950-1952 (Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Sav-Wil, 1950-1952 (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 9)
    - Finances, 1950 (Folder 10)
    - Finances Aug.-Sep., 1950 (Folder 11)
    - Governemnt Documents, 1950-1952 (Folder 12)
    - Maps, 1950-1952 (Folder 13)
    - Notes, 1950 (Folder 14)
    - Notes Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 15)
    - Publications, 1950 (Folder 16)
    - Publications, 1950-1951 (Folder 17)
    - Publications Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 18)
    - Survey Materials, 1949-1950 (Folder 19)
    - Survey Materials, 1950 (Folder 20)
    - Survey Materials Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 21)
    - Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 22)
    - Final Publication, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 22a)
  - Belgium, 1950-1952 (Box 1-3, Folder 23-126)
    Riegel conducted a study surveying belgians who participated in an educational exchange program with the United States, trying to answer whether educational exchange programs affect the participant's perception of the country they visited in the long term. This subseries contains materials related to that study including questionnaires, correspondents, data on participants, and publications.
    - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 23-61)
      Correspondents with Riegel in regards to his Belgium study often focused on the study's contents, findings, and were curious about its implications. Riegel corresponded with approximately 70 different individuals and wrote often to his family while in Belgium.
      - Abo-Ayd, 1950-1952 (Folder 23)
      - Bap-Bel, 1950-1952 (Folder 24)
      - Bie-Bra, 1950-1952 (Folder 25)
      - Bre-Buc, 1950-1952 (Folder 26)
      - Cantril, 1950-1951 (Folder 27)
      - Cantril, 1951-1952 (Folder 28)
      - Cantril, 1952-1953 (Folder 29)
      - Cantril Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 30)
      - Car-Chi, 1950-1952 (Folder 31)
      - Cle-Dey, 1950-1952 (Folder 32)
      - Dodds, 1950-1952 (Folder 33)
      - Domke, 1950-1952 (Folder 34)
      - DuB D'Yd, 1950-1952 (Folder 35)
      - Family Jun., 1951 (Folder 36)
      - Family Jul-Aug., 1951 (Folder 37)
      - Family Aug.-Sep., 1951 (Folder 38)
      - Fox-Ful, 1950-1952 (Folder 39)
      - Gal-Hei, 1950-1952 (Folder 40)
      - Her-Jon, 1950-1952 (Folder 41)
      - Info Request, 1950-1952 (Folder 42)
      - Kic-Lacoste, 1950-1952 (Folder 43)
      - Lacoste Jul.-Oct., 1951 (Folder 44)
      - Lacoste Oct.-Nov., 1951 (Folder 45)
      - Lacoste, 1951-1952 (Folder 46)
      - Lacoste, 1952-1953 (Folder 47)
      - Lance-Llo, 1950-1952 (Folder 48)
      - Mar-Opp, 1950-1952 (Folder 49)
      - Pai-Pyp, 1950-1952 (Folder 50)
      - Questionnaires, 1950-1952 (Folder 51)
      - Raë-Rus, 1950-1952 (Folder 52)
      - Recruitment, 1950-1952 (Folder 53)
      - San-Sto, 1950-1952 (Folder 54)
      - Str-Tho, 1950-1952 (Folder 55)
      - Tob-Van, 1950-1952 (Folder 56)
      - Wal-Wil, 1950-1952 (Folder 57)
      - Win-Zee, 1950-1952 (Folder 58)
      - Misc., 1950-1951 (Folder 59)
      - Misc. Jun.-Aug., 1951 (Folder 60)
      - Misc. Aug.-Nov., 1951 (Folder 61)
    - Finances, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 62-67)
      - Finances Mar.-Jun., 1951 (Folder 62)
      - Finances Jul.-Aug., 1951 (Folder 63)
      - Finances Aug.-Sep., 1951 (Folder 64)
      - Finances Sep.-Nov., 1951 (Folder 65)
      - Finances, 1952 (Folder 66)
      - Finances, 1950-1952 (Folder 67)
    - Notes, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 68-69)
      - Notes, 1950-1952 (Folder 68)
      - Notes, 1950-1952 (Folder 69)
    - Participants, 1950-1952 (Box 1-2, Folder 70-97)
      This subseries consists of materials related to every participant in Riegel's study of Belgium's cultural exchange program. Each person's listing has some responses to questions and occasionally some correspondence.
      - Ada-Blo, 1950-1952 (Folder 70)
      - Bor-Bou, 1950-1952 (Folder 71)
      - Bra-Buy, 1950-1952 (Folder 72)
      - Cat-Cro, 1950-1952 (Folder 73)
      - DeB-DeD, 1950-1952 (Folder 74)
      - Def-Dem, 1950-1952 (Folder 75)
      - DeP-Der, 1950-1952 (Folder 76)
      - Des-Deu, 1950-1952 (Folder 77)
      - Dew-Don, 1950-1952 (Folder 78)
      - Dro-Dup, 1950-1952 (Folder 79)
      - Dus-Evr, 1950-1952 (Folder 80)
      - Flo-Gal, 1950-1952 (Folder 81)
      - Gil-Gov, 1950-1952 (Folder 82)
      - Gra-Hal, 1950-1952 (Folder 83)
      - Hen-Jac, 1950-1952 (Folder 84)
      - Jou-Lab, 1950-1952 (Folder 85)
      - Lac-Lem, 1950-1952 (Folder 86)
      - Low-Mac, 1950-1952 (Folder 87)
      - Mar-Mun, 1950-1952 (Folder 88)
      - Par-Pol, 1950-1952 (Folder 89)
      - Rac-Sch, 1950-1952 (Folder 90)
      - Sch-Tav, 1950-1952 (Folder 91)
      - Tho-Vea, 1950-1952 (Folder 92)
      - Van Bla-Van Hee, 1950-1952 (Folder 93)
      - Van Heu- Vau, 1950-1952 (Folder 94)
      - Verd-Verh, 1950-1952 (Folder 95)
      - Web-Wil, 1950-1952 (Folder 96)
      - Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 97)
    - Publications, 1922-1952 (Box 2, Folder 98-104)
      Publications in this part of the collection focus on the effects and status of cultural exchange programs with the United States. Items of note in this subseries include a Belgian professor's analysis of Columbia University's geology courses from the 1920s, and statements by the state department about educational exchange programs.
      - Publications, 1922 (Folder 98)
      - Publications, 1943-1946 (Folder 99)
      - Publications, 1948-1950 (Folder 100)
      - Publications, 1950-1951 (Folder 101)
      - Publications, 1950 (Folder 102)
      - Publications, 1951-1952 (Folder 103)
      - Publications Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 104)
    - Publicity, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 105-110)
      This subseries consists of materials that were issued to spread the recognition and outreach of Riegel's study in Belgium. The majority of items are press releases informing individuals how they can participate and for participants to follow through with their questionnaires.
      - Publicity Jul.-Oct., 1950 (Folder 105)
      - Publicity, 1950-1951 (Folder 106)
      - Publicity Jan.-Feb., 1951 (Folder 107)
      - Publicity Feb.-Aug., 1951 (Folder 108)
      - Publicity Sep.-Dec., 1951 (Folder 109)
      - Publicity Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 110)
    - Survey Materials, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 111-122)
      This subseries consists of materials that were essential to Riegel's survey. Items of note in this subseries include Riegel's project proposal, sample questionnaires and instructions to participants and project assistants.
      - Project Proposal, 1950-1952 (Folder 111)
      - Instructions, 1950-1952 (Folder 112)
      - Instructions, 1950-1952 (Folder 113)
      - Lists, 1950-1952 (Folder 114)
      - Questionnaires Jul. 10-16, 1951 (Folder 115)
      - Questionnaires Jul. 16, 1951 (Folder 116)
      - Questionnaires Misc., 1951 (Folder 117)
      - Questionnaires misc., 1951 (Folder 118)
      - Questions 27-30, 1950-1952 (Folder 119)
      - Questions 31-33, 1950-1952 (Folder 120)
      - Questions 34-35, 1950-1952 (Folder 121)
      - Questions 36-37, 1950-1952 (Folder 122)
    - Misc., 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 123-126)
      - Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 123)
      - Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 124)
      - Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 125)
      - Misc., 1950-1952 (Folder 126)
  - Mobilizing for Chaos, 1934-1936 (Box 4, Folder 127-131)
    Riegel published a monograph, Mobilizing for Chaos, in 1934. In it he examined and explored the impact and importance of the use of propaganda in the contemporary world. He effectively explored the use of propaganda in nations such as pre-War Germany and its role in the rise of National Socialism and Adolf Hitler. This series contains material related to the publishing of the book, Mobilizing for Chaos. These materials primarily consist of book reviews, advertisements, and articles about Riegel's role in its creation.
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Reviews and Publicity, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 131)
- Propaganda, 1912-1992; 12.58 Linear Feet 7 large storage boxes, 2 oversize boxes, and 3 other boxes (Box 1-16, Folder 1-466)
  Items in this series are relevant to O. W. Riegel's involvement with propaganda materials from World War I through the Vietnam War. Within this series are correspondence between Riegel and his co-workers at the Office of War information, a variety of war leaflets, war themed news letters, foreign magazines, ephemeral propaganda materials, a few posters, Viet Cong banners, and German Newspapers. Some items and subjects of note include Hand made propaganda from the Viet Cong, A book of official japanese war leaflets, records from the Office of War Information, and pictoral records of the Spanish Civil War and the Second Sino Japanese War.
  Arrangement
  Some items have been removed from their appropriate folders and are located in oversize storage at the end of the series. Additionally, some books, magazines, and newspaper clippings are stored separately from the rest of the collection at this time. They are stored for the researcher's convenience and may be examined upon request.
  - World War I, 1914-1918 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
    Items in this subseries are relevant to the World War I era, and include Newspapers about the war, printed in 1914 and reprinted in the 1930's, Notes by Riegel about foreign and domestic propagada agencies, Photos of war figures and events with captions, and publications about the press and propaganda during the war.
    - Foreign Press, 1914 (Folder 1)
    - Newspapers, 1937 (Folder 2)
    - Newspapers, 1937 (Folder 3)
    - Notes, 1914-1937 (Folder 4)
    - Photos, 1914-1918 (Folder 5)
    - Publications, 1912-1918 (Folder 6)
  - Inter-War Period, 1918-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7-70)
    Th inter-war period subseries consists primarily of reports and publications from both the federal government and the private sector. Both of these groups focus heavily on propaganda, often comparing 1930s propaganda to propaganda during World War I. There is also some emphasis on the New Deal programs and their impact on the press and individual freedoms. Foreign Newspapers in this subseries tend to focus on Germany's shift to fascism and its implications. Also included in this subseries, are Riegel's own notes on these subjects mixed with brief personal comments related to his work.
    - Correspondence Bro-Vol, 1919-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Foreign News, 1919-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8-13)
      Items in this subseries consist of foreign press publications during the inter-war period. Newpapers and clippings are in French and German, and from the early 1930s.
      - French Aug. 20-27, 1933 (Folder 8)
      - French Aug.-Sep., 1933 (Folder 9)
      - French Misc, 1919-1939 (Folder 10)
      - German, 1933 (Folder 11)
      - German Aug., 1933 (Folder 12)
      - German Aug., 1933 (Folder 13)
    - Government Publications, 1919-1939 (Box 1, Folder 14-18)
      Goverment publications in this collection consist primarily of bills presented to congress, pages from the congressional record, and other sources oriented primarily around the use of the press prior to World War II.
      - Government Publications, 1926-1934 (Folder 14)
      - Government Publications Feb. 27, 1934 (Folder 15)
      - Government Publications Feb. 27, 1934 (Folder 16)
      - Government Publications, 1934-1938 (Folder 17)
      - Government Publications, 1940 (Folder 18)
    - Government Reports, 1919-1939 (Box 1, Folder 19-33)
      Government reports in this sub-series are issued often by executive agencies and are oriented around the press, propaganda, and considered regulation thereof. Reports include a discussion by the FCC over the "War of the Worlds Radio Broadcast", A report on Radio Broadcasting for Senator Burton Wheeler, and an agreement of journalistic standards by the Pan-American Congress of Journalists.
      - Department of Justice, 1934 (Folder 19)
      - Division of Press Intelligence, 1934 (Folder 20)
      - Federal Communications Commission, 1937-1938 (Folder 21)
      - Federal Communications Commission, 1938 (Folder 22)
      - Federal Communications Commission Oct.-Nov., 1938 (Folder 23)
      - Federal Communications Commission Nov.-Dec., 1938 (Folder 24)
      - Federal Trade Commission Nov.-Dec., 1934 (Folder 25)
      - Federal Trade Commission Dec., 1934 (Folder 26)
      - Foreign Affairs, 1932-1933 (Folder 27)
      - Pan-American Congress of Journalists Apr. 8-9, 1926 (Folder 28)
      - Pan-American Congress of Journalists Apr. 9-13, 1926 (Folder 29)
      - State Department, 1937 (Folder 30)
      - Miscellaneous, 1919-1939 (Folder 31)
      - Miscellaneous, 1919-1939 (Folder 32)
      - Miscellaneous, 1919-1939 (Folder 33)
    - Newspapers, 1919-1939 (Box 1, Folder 34-38)
      Newspapers in this sub-series focus on World War I propaganda, developments on Europe prior to the second World War, and Freedom of the Press.
      - Newspapers, 1932-1934 (Folder 34)
      - Newspapers Nov., 1934 (Folder 35)
      - Newspapers, 1935-1937 (Folder 36)
      - Newspapers, 1937-1938 (Folder 37)
      - Newspapers Miscellaneous, 1919-1939 (Folder 38)
    - Notes, 1919-1939 (Box 1, Folder 39-43)
      Riegel's notes from the Inter-war period focus on various journalism related topics, including: Telegraph cable, the politics of international press, the New Deal and Advertising, and other personal notes about his work.
      - Notes, 1929-1933 (Folder 39)
      - Notes, 1934-1939 (Folder 40)
      - Notes Miscellaneous, 1919-1939 (Folder 41)
      - Notes Miscellaneous, 1919-1939 (Folder 42)
      - Notes Miscellaneous, 1919-1939 (Folder 43)
    - Press Releases, 1919-1939 (Box 1, Folder 44-47)
      Press releases in this subseries address a variety of international and foreign relations topics such as the British Palestine mandate, the self-determination of the Saar Region, both pro and anti German perspectives on the national socialist government, and those who benefit from war.
      - Press Releases, 1934 (Folder 44)
      - Press Releases, 1935-1938 (Folder 45)
      - Press Releases, 1938-1940 (Folder 46)
      - Press Releases Miscellaneous, 1919-1939 (Folder 47)
    - Publications, 1919-1939 (Box 1, Folder 48-69)